pc-tablet.co.in 2019-09-01

# Privacy Policy - PC-Tablet IN

### Purpose of this Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how PC-Tablet treats the personally identifiable information that is collected about you when you visit the pc-tablet.com website. This policy also describes our treatment of personally identifiable information about you that our partners may share with us.

### What is Personally Identifiable Information

“Personally identifiable information” is information that we can use to identify you as an individual. Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, telephone number and any other information that is connected with your identity.

### Information This Privacy Policy Does Not Apply to

This privacy policy does not apply to information collected about you by anyone except PC-Tablet. Any information you provide when you visit websites other than pc-tablet.com or when you purchase any products or services that may be offered or advertised on pc-tablet.com by companies other than PC-Tablet is subject to the privacy policies of the third-party organizations who run and/or own these websites.

### Information We Collect

  * Non-Registered Users: Certain content and tools on the pc-tablet.com Web site, such as news articles, pictures, graphics, stock quotes, are available to all users without registration. PC-Tablet does not collect any personally identifiable information from you when you visit these areas of the pc-tablet.com Web site.
  * Editorial Contributions, Promotions, and Surveys: Contributions, surveys, and other promotions may be offered on the pc-tablet.com Web site. In conjunction with such contribution requests or surveys, we may ask pc-tablet.com participants for personally identifiable information related to the topic of the survey, an entry in the promotion, prize notification or fulfillment.
  * Website Usage Information: PC-Tablet automatically collects IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit the pc-tablet.com website. This information helps us evaluate how our users navigate and use our Web site.

### How Long We Retain Your Data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

### Use Of Information

PC-Tablet uses personally identifiable information collected from you for the following general purposes: To fulfill your requests for specific products and services; To customize the advertising and content you see; To improve the design and content of our site; To contact you about special offers, products or services that may be of interest to you; To enter you in editorial contributions or promotions at your specific request; To provide you with customer service.

### Where We Send Your Data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### Information Sharing And Disclosure

pc-tablet.com will not sell, share or otherwise disclose any personally identifiable information about our current or former web site users to third party companies or individuals, except as permitted or required by law. PC-Tablet may share or disclose personally identifiable information about you to other companies or individuals when: We have your consent to share the information; We utilize third-party service providers to provide products, services or functions on our behalf (such as sending emails or processing credit cards), and require these service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information and not to use your personally identifiable information for any reason except to carry out the purpose(s) for which we hired them; We need to protect our legal rights (for example, if we are trying to collect money you owe us or we are trying to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreement with you); Aggregate information is information that we (or third-party service providers on our behalf) collect about pc-tablet.com Web site users on an anonymous basis. We may share aggregated demographic and usage information with our prospective and actual business partners, advertisers and other third parties.

### Cookies

pc-tablet.com (or third-party service providers on our behalf) may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small amount of data (often including a unique identifier), that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. pc-tablet.com uses cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to identify you as a registered user, personalize your experience at our site, save your password in password-protected areas, and display relevant content, products, services, and advertising. To the extent that PC-Tablet utilizes third-party service providers to set and access cookies on the computer of our website users on behalf of PC-Tablet, we require such service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of the information collected and not to use such information for any reason except to carry out the purpose(s) for which we hired them. We use reputable third parties to present or serve some or all of the advertisements on our website. These third-party network advertisers may set and access their own cookies on your computer. The use of cookies by third parties is subject to such third party’s own privacy policies. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allow the user to reject cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features offered through our Website.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Your Cookie Choices And How To Opt-Out

You have the choice whether to accept the use of Cookies and we have explained how you can exercise your rights below.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept HTTP cookies. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, and how to disable existing cookies. For more information about HTTP cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at [Your Ad Choices](http://optout.aboutads.info/?lang=EN&c=2#!/).

Most browsers are initially set up to accept HTTP cookies. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, and how to disable existing cookies. For more information about HTTP cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

We are not responsible for the effectiveness of any such opt-out options. California residents are entitled to know the effects of opt-out options under California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b)(7). The effect of an opt-out, if successful, will be to stop targeted advertising, but it will still allow the collection of usage data for certain purposes (e.g., research, analytics and internal Site operation purposes).

Controlling the HTML5 local storage on your browser depends on which browser you use. For more information regarding your specific browser, please consult the browser’s website (often in the “Help” section).

Please note, however, that without HTTP cookies and HTML5 and Flash local storage, you may not be able to take full advantage of all our Site features and parts of the Site will not function properly.

Please note that rejecting Cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our Site.

### Security

Your pc-tablet.com registration information is password-protected for your privacy and security. The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited-access servers. We maintain (directly and through our agents) physical, electronic and procedural security safeguards to protect your personally identifiable information.

### What Rights You Have Over Your Data

If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

### Review and Changes

We update this Privacy Policy from time to time in our discretion and will notify you of any material changes to the way in which we treat Personal Data, by posting a notice on relevant areas of the Services. We will also provide notice to you in other ways in our discretion, such as through contact information you have provided. Any updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy unless otherwise specified. Your continued use of the Services after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy (or such other act specified at that time) will constitute your consent to those changes. However, we will not, without your consent, use your Personal Data in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time your Personal Data was collected.

### Children

The Services are intended for a general audience and are not intended for and should not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and we do not target the Services to children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us using the details in the Contact Us section below. We will delete such information from our files as soon as reasonably practicable.

### Contacting The Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us or email us at  _support@pc-tablet.com_.
